http://www.dvo.com/privacy.php

DVO Enterprises Privacy Policy
DVO Enterprises is committed to protecting the privacy and security of its online visitors. This policy statement provides our visitors with an overview of the measures we have taken to provide a safe environment for everyone.
PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION
We consider the following, among other things, to be personally identifiable information: first and last name, e-mail address, street address and phone number.
We may request such personally identifiable information from our visitors to process and fulfill orders for products or services and in connection with contests, sweepstakes, product registration, newsletter subscription, and visitors' requests for information.
NON-PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION AND THE USE OF COOKIE TECHNOLOGY
We collect non-personally identifiable information through the use of a software technology called "cookies," and through our visitors' voluntary submissions to us and/or upon our request. By non-personally identifiable information, we are referring to information about our visitors' browsers (e.g., Netscape Navigator or Internet Explorer), operating systems (e.g., Windows or Macintosh), Internet service providers (e.g., AOL or NET.COM) and other similar information which we track in aggregate form.
Cookie technology helps us to know how many people visit us and where visitors go on our site. Cookies are small bits of information we send to your computer. Among other things, this non-personally identifiable information allows us to know which areas are favorites, which areas need a bit of improvement, or what technologies and Internet services are being used by our visitors so that we may continually improve our visitors' online experiences.
USE OF IP ADDRESSES
We collect IP addresses to obtain aggregate information on the use of dvo.com. An IP address is a number assigned to your computer by a Web server when you're on the Web. When you are on our site, we have a back-end server that logs your computer's IP address. We only use the information we find out from tracking IP addresses in the aggregate, such as how many users entered a specific area of our site, and not to track a specific IP address to identify an individual user. However, we may use such information to identify a user if we feel that there are or may be safety and/or security issues or to comply with legal requirements.
SECURITY
DVO Enterprises ensures that all personally and non-personally identifiable information that it receives via the Internet is secure against unauthorized access. This information is kept in a safe and secure system isolated from direct connection to the Internet. We will give out personal information as required by law, for example to comply with a court order or subpoena or to assist in criminal investigations. We may also give out personal information when we deem it advisable in order to protect the safety and security of our sites and visitors to our sites.
Why are we so safe?
DVO Enterprises uses secure server software over a Secure Socket Layer (SSL) line to protect your credit card information. It encrypts all of your personal and credit card information so that this information cannot be read as it travels to our ordering system, and once it is received, it is stored in a location not accessible via the Internet.
Sign Up for Free!
Sign Up for Free!
Sign Up
#1 Best-Selling Recipe App with millions and millions served!
